## **f** integrify



# PHAM HUY QUANG

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

LINKEDIN

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Fluent
- Finnish Novice
- Vietnamese Native

## **PROFILE**

A fourth-year Information Technology student. Experienced in Web Development having worked with up-to-date technologies such as ES6, React with Hooks and Redux, MongoDB. Have also completed fromjects in C# / .NET and React Native. In addition, proficient in applying agile methodologies, version control and project management tracking tools when participating in projects.

## **RECENT PROJECTS**

#### Practice backend project

Node.js, MongoDB, Mongo Atlas

A back-end project using the aforementioned technologies to simulate common operations and procedures. This is a personal project.

#### **To-do Project**

JavaScript, React, ESLint, Prettier

A project that lets users add to-do actions, displays the list of all the actions and allows to delete said actions. This is a personal project.

#### **Country App**

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, React Hooks, Redux

A project that fetched data from the public REST Countries API. This project was completed during the training at Integrify.

## **SKILLS**

Front-end: HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript (ES5 an ES6), TypeScript, React, Redux.

Back-end: Node.js, Express.js, C#, .NET.

Mobile: React Native (Expo).

Database: MongoDB, Mongo Atlas.

Testing: ESLint, Prettier, Jest.

DevOps: Git, GitHub.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | January 2020 - Present

#### Mobile Developer (Project Worker)

Ammantis Oy | Vaasa, Finland | September 2019 - December 2019

- Built a server on the hardware part of the application.
- · Built two screens for the mobile application.
- Used Redmine as the project management tracking tool, Git and Github for version control, and agile software development (Scrum) when working on this application.
- Technologies used: React Native, ESLint + Prettier, MongoDB.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **B.Eng.** in Information Technology

Vaasa University of Applied Sciences (VAMK) | Vaasa, Finland | September 2016 - July 2020